

CONTACT

Paku, Azerbaijan



nikita8192@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/nikita-nefedov

github.com/nefedovnd

SKILLS

- Data analysis
- MS Excel (VBA)
- Python (machine, deep learning)
- SQL
- Tableau
- STATA
- Financial audit
- Analytical reports
- Presentations
- MS Powerpoint
- Political science
- Public opinion
- Survey analysis
- Scientific research
- Project management
- Design visualization
- 2D/3D Adobe

LANGUAGES

English: fluent

German: basic (in progress)

Russian: native

Nikita Nefedov

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Initiative, responsible and time-managing person with a range of practical and theoretical experience in the data analysis and financial control. Academically qualified in politics, public opinion and data analysis. Experienced in working in extreme conditions, able to dive into any topic in the shortest possible time with high attention to detail, carry out in-depth work on project management, conduct analytical reports and presentations.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Head Financial Control Directorate - Moscow, Russia2/2021 - 11/2022Advisor of an expert and analytical department7/22 - 11/22Senior Specialist of the Department of Expert Analytical Activities11/21 - 7/22Leading Specialist of the Department of Expert Analytical Activities7/21 - 11/21

- Data analysis and financial audit.
- Implementation of control in the financial and budgetary sphere, procurement, social sector (healthcare, urban construction, education).
- Conduction of anti-corruption and anti-monopoly investigations.
- Evaluation of the effectiveness of the disposal of organizations of their budgetary funds.
- Political, legislative and legal analysis.

Moscow City Innovation Agency - Moscow, Russia

10/2020 - 12/2020

Intern

- Consulting in the field of technology development and innovative entrepreneurship.
- Monitoring of the innovation market and development of plans for cooperation with key partners.
- Organization of industry forums.

UN Online Volunteering service - Colchester, England

4/2019 - 6/2019

Volunteer

• Participated in development of Tanzanian infrastructure, managed IT software.

EDUCATION

University of Essex - Colchester, England

2014 - 2019

Master of Arts: Public Opinion and Political Behaviour (with distinction)

2018 - 2019

- Average mark:
- Dissertation project has a first-class mark "Survey analysis of individual economic perception effect on public attitudes towards immigration and variation of attitudes across social classes."
- Qualification modules include: Public Opinion and Political Behaviour, Quantitative Political analysis, Data analysis, Survey analysis, Conflict Resolution, International Negotiations, Theory and Explanation in Political Science

Bachelor of Arts: Political Science

2015 - 2018

- Average mark: 2.1
- President of the University Society (2 terms)

Foundation Degree: Politics 2014 – 2015

CERTIFICATES

 $\label{lem:python_squared} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A & A & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & Python & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabular}{ll} Python & A \\ \hline \end{tabular} \begin{tabula$